The longer I drift upon these rails
mayoi no naka de
The greater the longing in my soul grows
dandan ookiku naru kokoro no sakebi
Can't you hear its terrible wails?
hitori janai tte
I'm thinking it's time to lay my head where it's not quite as cold
kanjiru basho ga hoshii hajimari nan da
storm on heart
Come on
Feel that urge boil
tsuyoi shoudou
Show the world all that's boiling in you
tsuyoi dake ja nai sonna shoudou
Come on
Go ahead, turn around
furimuite mo
The answer's gonna be no, no, no!
kotaeru koe wa no no no
Someone tell me
wakaranai
How to make myself anew
atarashii jibun e to
Who knew the key to change was right here all along?
kawaru tame no kagi wa koko ni aru
Let the fierce winds batter me
mukai kaze ni utarete mo
Let the freezing rains soak me
tsumetai ame ni nurete mo
This ever-burning fire in my belly will keep me racing on
kienai jounetsu de hashirou
Hope is like the rising sun
negai wa hikari no you ni
Bright and burning
ashita wo terasu
It brings tomorrow to us
terasu yo
Now show me what you're made of, people
saa kakugo wo misete goran yo
There's a rail stretching straight to
isshun no shinkirou ga
Tomorrow and into the sun
massugu ni nobiru rail wo
If you can see it
utsushita no sa